{
    "subject": "resource/Sidney_Toler",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthName",
    "object": "Hooper G. Toler, Jr.",
    "human_readable": "Sidney Toler's birth name was Hooper G. Toler, Jr.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.987622082233429,
            "question": "Was Sidney Toler born as Hooper G. Toler Jr.?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.918620765209198,
            "question": "What was Sidney Toler's birth name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9125084280967712,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Sidney Toler and Hooper G. Toler Jr.?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.880821168422699,
            "question": "What is Hooper G. Toler Jr. known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8614481687545776,
            "question": "Did Sidney Toler use his birth name professionally?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.783251941204071,
            "question": "How did Sidney Toler's birth name differ from his professional name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7401057481765747,
            "question": "What is the full name of Sidney Toler?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6966540813446045,
            "question": "Is Sidney Toler a stage name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.07472556829452515,
            "question": "Can you provide examples of other famous people who changed their names professionally?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.05443139001727104,
            "question": "What are some common reasons for actors to use stage names?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sidney Toler's birth name was Hooper G. Toler, Jr.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1959_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you provide examples of other famous people who changed their names professionally?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1959_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Sidney Toler a stage name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1959_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the full name of Sidney Toler?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1959_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1959_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1959_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1959_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1959_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1959_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1959_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1959_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1959_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1959_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1959_79.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information provided supports the triple that Sidney Toler's birth name was Hooper G. Toler, Jr., as it is mentioned in multiple documents that his full name at birth was indeed Hooper G. Toler Jr."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that confirms Sidney Toler\u2019s birth name was Hooper G. Toler, Jr., which is supported by the text in multiple files, such as \"file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1959/re-ranker-msmarco/2.txt\" and \"file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1959/re-ranker-msmarco/19.txt\"."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}